{
  "answers" : {
    "-KEJ2MQftqtfSnbwTzdU" : {
      "author" : "Yoshi",
      "date" : "Fri Apr 01 2016",
      "downVotes" : 0,
      "question" : "-KEIPf3E_bQUOEEdEfhV",
      "theAnswer" : "Really Big",
      "upVotes" : 0
    },
    "-KEJ2Q3cAaK5fGPZousg" : {
      "author" : "Tim",
      "date" : "Fri Apr 01 2016",
      "downVotes" : 0,
      "question" : "-KEIPf3E_bQUOEEdEfhV",
      "theAnswer" : "About the size of California",
      "upVotes" : 0
    },
    "-KEJ5YJuT6hAlUp3guOo" : {
      "author" : "ok",
      "date" : "Fri Apr 01 2016",
      "downVotes" : 0,
      "question" : "-KEIPf3E_bQUOEEdEfhV",
      "theAnswer" : "test",
      "upVotes" : 0
    },
    "-KEJFK3cMc3JQ9CiTdlW" : {
      "author" : "ted",
      "date" : "Fri Apr 01 2016",
      "downVotes" : 0,
      "question" : "-KEJFGoOxBo-o_YIkF3D",
      "theAnswer" : "mario",
      "upVotes" : 0
    },
    "-KEJFSxuAXzdT7NcVVo5" : {
      "author" : "neil",
      "date" : "Fri Apr 01 2016",
      "downVotes" : 0,
      "question" : "-KEJFPYJeMsa7YZPGBvq",
      "theAnswer" : "ember g helper helper-name",
      "upVotes" : 0
    }
  },
  "questions" : {
    "-KEIPf3E_bQUOEEdEfhV" : {
      "answers" : {
        "-KEJ2MQftqtfSnbwTzdU" : true,
        "-KEJ2Q3cAaK5fGPZousg" : true,
        "-KEJ5YJuT6hAlUp3guOo" : true
      },
      "author" : "some kid",
      "date" : "Fri Apr 01 2016",
      "downVotes" : 0,
      "notes" : "also is it made of cheese?",
      "tag" : "stupid",
      "theQuestion" : "How big is Japan?",
      "upVotes" : 0
    },
    "-KEJ2EtDgg-fdZCI_HEH" : {
      "author" : "Neil",
      "date" : "Fri Apr 01 2016",
      "downVotes" : 0,
      "notes" : "lololol",
      "tag" : "stupid",
      "theQuestion" : "How many licks does it take to get to the center of a tootsie pop",
      "upVotes" : 0
    },
    "-KEJ82Xoa_-7Xe4FQx7q" : {
      "author" : "Neil",
      "date" : "Fri Apr 01 2016",
      "downVotes" : 0,
      "notes" : "Like is it over and junk?",
      "tag" : "tech",
      "theQuestion" : "Is moore's law dead?",
      "upVotes" : 0
    },
    "-KEJFGoOxBo-o_YIkF3D" : {
      "answers" : {
        "-KEJFK3cMc3JQ9CiTdlW" : true
      },
      "author" : "Bob",
      "date" : "Fri Apr 01 2016",
      "downVotes" : 0,
      "notes" : "Any system any gen",
      "tag" : "games",
      "theQuestion" : "What's the best video game ever?",
      "upVotes" : 0
    },
    "-KEJFPYJeMsa7YZPGBvq" : {
      "answers" : {
        "-KEJFSxuAXzdT7NcVVo5" : true
      },
      "author" : "Neil",
      "date" : "Fri Apr 01 2016",
      "downVotes" : 0,
      "notes" : "",
      "tag" : "code",
      "theQuestion" : "How do you add helpers in ember?",
      "upVotes" : 0
    }
  }
}
